import { Question } from "../contestantControls";

export const katieQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 76,
    question: "What is Sheldon's famous catchphrase after his classic pranks?",
    options: ["Bazooka!", "Bazinga!", "Tazdingo!"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 77,
    question: "Where is the Big Bang Theory set?",
    options: ["Pasadena, California", "Trenton, New Jersey", "San Jose, California"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 78,
    question: "What university do the 4 main male characters work at?",
    options: ["MIT", "Harvard", "Caltech"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 79,
    question: "What male character is made fun of for looking like a Beatles member?",
    options: ["Leonard Hofsteder", "Georgie Cooper", "Howard Wolowitz"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 80,
    question: "What is Sheldon's Fianc√©e's name?",
    options: ["Bernadette", "Amy", "Emily"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 81,
    question: "What character is only heard but never shown?",
    options: ["Raj's mum", "Howard's mum", "Sheldon's mum"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 82,
    question: "Who plays Sheldon Cooper?",
    options: ["Jim Parsons", "Tom Farhorn", "Lee Curtis"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 83,
    question: "What is the prequel show that followed the Big Bang Theory?",
    options: ["Sheldon Time", "Young Sheldon", "The adventures of George Cooper"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 84,
    question: "How many seasons of The Big Bang Theory are there?",
    options: ["15", "14", "12"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 85,
    question: "Who is the first main female character introduced?",
    options: ["Penny", "Amy", "Alesha"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 86,
    question: "When did the Big Bang Theory first air?",
    options: ["2009", "2007", "2008"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 87,
    question: "When did the Big Bang Theory finish?",
    options: ["2021", "2018", "2019"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 88,
    question: "What is the space station orbiting above the earth called?",
    options: ["ISS", "Starlink", "Hubble"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 89,
    question: "How many dimensions does the most complete string theory model predict?",
    options: ["10", "8", "11"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 90,
    question: "What country are Russian Soyuz capsules launched from?",
    options: ["Mongolia", "Kazakhstan", "Belarus"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  }
];